(Raj:)It's, like,
the best one they make,
(Raj:)I just can't get it to work.
I'll figure it out.
(Raj:)It streams HD video straight
to your phone while it's flying.
(Howard:)Nice.
(Howard:)Where were you
when I was single?
(Leonard:)Okay, we should leave in
about an hour. You all packed?
(Penny:)Uh, yeah, I just need to throw
in a few last minute things--
(Penny:)you know, makeup,
underwear, clothes.
(Sheldon:)If your bathroom floor
(Sheldon:)counts as a carry-on,
you're packed.
(Amy:)Leonard,
have you ever given
(Amy:)a high school
commencement speech before?
(Leonard:)Nope. It's pretty exciting.
(Sheldon:)Aren't you afraid
of being blinded?
(Leonard:)How would I be blinded?
(Sheldon:)At the end of the ceremony,
(Sheldon:)all the students throw
those pointy hats in the air.
(Sheldon:)It's all pomp and circumstance
(Sheldon:)until someone loses an eye.
(Leonard:)I'll take my chances.
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)I wonder if they make
"I told you so"
cards in braille.
(Raj:)Look, the problem
with commencement speeches
(Raj:)is that they're boring.
(Raj:)Ooh, do you own
a T-shirt cannon?
(Howard:)Why would he own
(Raj:)I don't know. Why do I own one?
(Amy:)I think it's really nice
(Amy:)that you're sharing
this experience with Penny.
(Leonard:)Mm, I thought
it'd be fun
(Leonard:)to show her my old
stomping grounds.
(Leonard:)I even know the exact spot
where they used to stomp me.
(Bernadette:)Well, now you
get to go back
(Bernadette:)as a successful
scientist.
(Amy:)With a beautiful girl
on your arm.
(Sheldon:)And a pointy hat sticking
out of your eyeball.